Hi, this is Liz Muller from Liz Hair Design in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip I'm going to show you how to make a pony tail.
We have nice, pretty hair here.
We're going to go ahead and brush it and make it nice and soft and easy to manage when we do the pony tail.
Now, depends on how you want to wear your pony tail.
If you want to wear the pony tail high, you come up high like this, and it's really great for the young people, they usually love to wear their pony tail's high, especially young girls, high school girls, and cheerleader's, and all that stuff.
They usually wear the pony tail's real, real high.
You want to take it and brush it, make it neat.
This is actually in the middle of the head.
You can take it and put it in there like that, little band for the hair.
You've got yourself a medium sized cute pony tail.
Look how nice her hair is, it's fluffy. You see, now that's me, that's right in the middle. It can go up here in the middle of the head, it can go even lower than that, OK. Business women wear theirs a little low sometimes, all the way down here.
This is is Liz Muller, and this is how to make a pony tail.